Guide to the Brown Brothers Harriman Records 1696-1973, 1995 (bulk, 1820-1968) MS 78
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Partners' Papers (1859-1966), 7.8 Linear feet 14.5 document boxes, 34 volumes
  - Subseries C. Thatcher M. Brown Papers (1890-1966), 4.5 Linear feet 10 ms. boxes and 4 volumes
    - Subseries C.i. Personal and Family Materials (1890-1966)
      The letters of Montagu Norman, who was a Brown Brothers partner and Governor of the Bank of England, to Caro Noyes Brown are affectionate and often apologetic for not having written sooner. After 1933, letters from his wife Priscilla include descriptions of life in pre-war and wartime Britain. The correspondence was used by Sir Henry Clay in researching his 1957 biography Lord Norman and includes notes from Clay at that time.
      Letters during World War II to Thatcher and Caro Brown from Gertrude Balfour (1877-1970), who was Montagu Norman's sister and the wife of Scottish botanist Alistair Balfour (1873-1945), have text cut out where they were redacted by the censor.
      Much of Thatcher Brown's personal material pertains to the estates of family members for whom he served as executor, including his brother James Crosby Brown, cousin Moreau Delano, and wife Caro Noyes Brown. As part of his brother's estate, Thatcher Brown donated the Pasque Island property deeds to Dukes County Historical Society (now the Martha's Vineyard Museum) and sold the property to then Massachusetts Governor Forbes. He corresponded extensively with family members and with staff at Green-Wood Cemetery, Brooklyn, regarding the upkeep and improvement of various family plots there.
      The correspondence with his brother William Adams Brown is mostly to do with managing the latter's investments, but also discusses a loan of their mother Mary Elizabeth Adams Brown's instruments from the Metropolitan Museum. William Adams Brown's 1933 letters after a visit to Germany record his impressions of the political and economic situation there and include some newspaper clippings in German.
      Correspondence with his son Daniel Noyes Brown is likewise mostly to do with investments, but the 1943 letters detail Daniel's experience while serving in the military in North Africa.
      An English impression of the impending war is provided in the 1939 letters from Edward Clifton-Brown; his wartime letters record conditions on the home front as well as the whereabouts of various family members and firm employees.
      Thatcher Brown's personal involvement with fundraising and other efforts for charitable institutions in around New York City is reflected in the records for the Building Fund of Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church; during his service as treasurer of 1st Presbyterian Church in Rumson, New Jersey; and with St. Cloud Church, where his mother had had a marker installed after the demolition of a spring house provided by her husband John Crosby Brown. The church's Men's Club had been established with funds from the John Crosby Brown estate.
      Thatcher and Caro Brown initially rented an apartment at 139 east 79th street, which was later converted to a cooperative plan. Thatcher Brown helped to form that plan, served on the building's Board, and Mrs. Brown owned half of the proprietary lease on the commercial property on the building's ground floor.
      Chester Jay Hunt was a Yale classmate (1897) of Thatcher Brown's who wrote many letters detailing his financial woes while running a bulb-growing company and later about the inadequacies of his New Jersey state pension. Thatcher Brown assisted him with job possibilities, took up a collection for his benefit from Yale classmates, loaned him money, and made frequent gifts of cash and checks. He also corresponded extensively over the same period with fellow Yale Fund class agent George Parmly Day about the class's charitable efforts on behalf of Hunt.
      In 1950, Brown had privately printed and distributed Brown Brothers & Co. [and] Brown Brothers Harriman & Co., 1900-1950, a continuation of his father's account of the firm's first 100 years. Copies of the book that were with the related correspondence are now included in Series X. Published Material.
      Caro Noyes Brown's bride's book (Volume 60) for her June 3, 1904, marriage in St. Paul, Minnesota, includes signatures of ushers and bridesmaids from the Adams, Moore, Coe, Brown, and Delano families. Her 1929 diary (Volume 61) is from a trip to South America, during which her husband was guest of honor at dinner given by the Mayor of Lima, Peru (see illustration on p. 195 of Partners in Banking).
      The household inventory in Volume 62 is illustrated with pencil sketches of individual items and annotated with their location in Thatcher Brown's homes (775 Park Avenue in 1932; 139 east 79th Street in 1943), purchase prices, provenance, and any disposition after sale.
      Thatcher Brown served as executor, financial and investment advisor, and banker for many members of the extended Brown, Delano, and Noyes families, including his cousins, nieces, and nephews.
      A son of John Crosby Brown, Thatcher Brown's siblings were William Adams Brown (1865-1943), Eliza Coe Brown (called Bessie, 1868-1959), Mary Magoun Brown (1869-1962), James Crosby Brown (1872-1930), and Amy Brighthurst Brown (1878-1960).
      In 1892, William Adams Brown (1865-1943) married Helen Gilman Noyes, whose sister Caro Lord Noyes would marry Thatcher Brown in 1904. William and Helen Noyes Brown's children were John Crosby Brown (1892-1950), William Adams Brown (1894-1957), Winthrop Gilman Brown (1907-1987), and Helen Adams Brown (1910-1928). In 1936 William Adams Brown retired after 40 years on the faculty at Union Theological Seminary.
      Eliza Coe Brown married Edward Caldwell Moore (b. 1857) in 1887 and their three children were Dorothea May Moore (1884-1995), who in 1941 married Arthur Burkhard (1891-1973); John Crosby Brown Moore (1897-1993), principal of the architectural firm of Dunham and Moore in New York City; and Elizabeth Ripley Moore (1907-1983).
      Mary Magoun Brown trained as a nurse at Presbyterian Hospital and began her career in 1899 on the staff of the Henry Street Settlement Visiting Nursing. She retired in 1951 after 50 years of service.
      James Crosby Brown died unexpectedly in 1930, leaving a large and complicated estate valued, even after the stock market crash of 1929, at over $1.5 million, and of which Thatcher Brown was executor. It included Clifton Wynyates, a 194 acre property in Ardmore, Pennsylvania, as well as land on Pasque Island, Massachusetts. After his death, his widow moved from the Pennsylvania property, and by 1933 it was being subdivided by developers Durham and James.
      In 1898 James Crosby Brown had married Mary Agnes Hewlett (1875-1919) and had two sons: James Crosby Brown (called Crosby, 1903-1965) and Alexander Crosby Brown (called Alec, 1905-1993). In 1921, he married Aurelia Gladys Pomeroy Jenkins (1883-1938), the widow of a Yale classmate and mother of Allston Jenkins (called Allie, 1903-1994). The guardian of their daughter, Aurelia Clifton Brown (called Thistle, b. 1925), after her mother's death was her half-brother Allston (who was also executor of his mother's estate), and she lived at one time with her uncle Thatcher Brown.
      Amy Brighthurst Brown (1878-1960) married Henry Lockwood de Forest (1875-1954) in 1899 and had three children: May de Forest (1902-1990); Emily Johnston de Forest (1903-1977), whose second husband was Leslie Tillotson Webster (1893-1943); and Robert Weeks de Forest, who died at birth in September, 1909. Henry Lockwood de Forest's sister Frances Emily (b. 1878) was the wife of William Adams Walker Stewart.
      Caro Lord Noyes Brown's (1876-1947) mother, Helen Gilman Noyes, was the sister of Serena Hale Davenport. Caro and Thatcher Brown's three children were Moreau Delano Brown (1905-1974), who became a Brown Brothers Harriman partner in 1939; Daniel Noyes Brown (1906-1985), who trained as a physician at Columbia University; and Thatcher Magoun Brown (1908-1983).
      The children of Thatcher Brown's maternal aunt and uncle Sarah Magoun Adams and Brown Brothers partner Eugene Delano included partner Moreau Delano (1877-1936; see Subseries I.C.vi. Partners); William Adams Delano (1874-1960), the architect of, among many other buildings, the Rockefeller estate Kykuit, Otto Kahn's Oheka, and Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney's Old Westbury studio; Caroline Delano (called Lina), who married Dr. Augustus B. Wadsworth and was the mother of Eugene Delano Wadsworth; Augustus Baldwin Wadsworth; and botanist and supporter of Harvard University's Arnold Arboretum, Susan Adams Delano McKelvey (1883-1964).
      In London, partner Edward Clifton-Brown (1870-1944; see Subseries I.C.vi. Partners) was a great-grandson of Sir William Brown (1784-1864,) who established the family firm in Liverpool. Edward's paternal uncle was London partner Sir Alexander Hargreaves Brown (1844-1922; see Subseries I.C.vi. Partners); his son was Anthony Clifton-Brown (1903-1984).
      The subseries is arranged chronologically; within the chronological arrangement, many of the subjects have multiple files bearing the same title, which are themselves organized chronologically.
      Placed at the beginning of the series is an annotated inventory of the carton containing personal correspondence of Thatcher Brown, originally in the possession of his son Moreau D. Brown, from which these materials were taken.
      Various blueprints of grave markers from Green-Wood Cemetery have been removed to oversized boxes listed at the end of the subseries.
      - "Correspondence of Mr. Thatcher Brown": annotated list, Undated (Offsite-box 99, Folder 12)
      - John Crosby Brown estate: agreements and heirs documents, 1890-1918 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 13)
      - John Crosby Brown estate: will, executors' accounting, suit, 1909, 1911, 1912 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 14)
      - Letters to Caro Noyes from her family; dance card, 1894-1896 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 15)
      - Caro Noyes letters to her parents, 1898 October 7 - 1899 August (Offsite-box 100, Folder 1)
      - Thatcher M. Brown diary, 1899 summer (Offsite-box 100, Folder 2)
      - Letters to Caro Noyes Brown from Montagu Norman; 1952 cover letter from biographer Sir Henry Clay, 1907-1933, 1952, undated (Offsite-box 100, Folder 3)
      - St. Cloud Presbyterian Church, West Orange, NJ, 1911-1951 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 4)
      - Mary Elizabeth Adams Brown estate: inventory of Seal Harbor cottage; appraisal and inventory of Brighthurst; 36 E. 37th street inventory, 1912, undated (Offsite-box 100, Folder 5)
      - Mary Elizabeth Adams Brown estate: settlement, 1923 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 6)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: Philadelphia property at 4th and Chestnut streets, 1920, 1930 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 7)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: partners' file correspondence with Philadelphia office, 1929-1942 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 8)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: correspondence with Allston Jenkins, 1930-1932 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 9)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: correspondence with Allston Jenkins, 1933-1937 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 10)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: correspondence with Allston Jenkins, 1938-1946 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 11)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: guardian account for Aurelia Clifton Brown, 1931-1953 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 1)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: property settlements and sales, 1934-1936 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 2)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: property settlements and sales, 1937-1940 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 3)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: property settlements and sales, 1941-1944 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 4)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: Ardmore property, correspondence with developers Durham and Irvine (Offsite-box 101, Folder 5)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: donation of Pasque Island deed to Dukes County Historical Society; Forbes correspondence, 1936, 1941 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 6)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: subdivision and sales, correspondence with real estate brokers Hirst & MacFarland, 1936-1941, 1944 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 7)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: finances, 1941-1949 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 8)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: settlement of amount due from Durham & Irvine, 1944 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 9)
      - First Presbyterian Church, Rumson, New Jersey, 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 10)
      - Grand jury service, 1927-1946 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 1)
      - William Adams Brown, 1931-1943 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Warehouse: storage of car and personal items, 1931-1947 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 3)
      - Eliza Coe Brown Moore (Offsite-box 102, Folder 4)
      - 59 Wall Street deed donation to Museum of the City of New York; New York Public Library Bulletin on Brown Brothers ledger donation, 1932 March, 1936 June (Offsite-box 102, Folder 5)
      - Alexander Crosby Brown, 1932-1933, 1951 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence from Priscilla Norman; account of journey with enemy aliens, 1933, 1938-1944 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 7)
      - Powers of attorney from and to Daniel Noyes Brown and Thatcher M. Brown, Jr., 1933, 1942, 1944, 1952 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 8)
      - Essex County Country Club; St. George's Society of New York, 1934, 1944, 1952 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 9)
      - Moreau Delano estate, 1936-1938 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence with Dr. John H. Cunningham about Pasque Island, Massachusetts, 1938 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 11)
      - Dorothea May Moore, 1938 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 12)
      - Caroline Delano Wadsworth, 1938 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 13)
      - William Adams Delano, 1938, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 14)
      - Susan Adams Delano McKelvey, 1938-1953 (Offsite-box 102, Drawer 15)
      - Edward Clifton-Brown, 1939-1953 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 16)
      - Grove Reformed Church, Clifton, New Jersey: gift of John Crosby Brown property, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 17)
      - Serena Hale Davenport estate, 1940-1942 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 18)
      - Union Theological Seminary; Harkness bequest, 1940, 1945, 1947, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 102, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence to Caro Noyes Brown from Gertrude Balfour, 1941-1943 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 1)
      - Daniel Noyes Brown, 1942-1949 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 2)
      - 139 east 79th street: co-op conversion, leases, 1942-1945 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 3)
      - 139 east 79th street: correspondence with Brown, Wheelock, Harris, Stevens; New York Telephone Company, 1942-1947 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 4)
      - 139 east 79th street: rent and maintenance receipts, 1943-1954 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 5)
      - 139 east 79th street: store leases, 1945 September (Offsite-box 103, Folder 6)
      - 139 east 79th street: co-op business, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 7)
      - 139 east 79th street: co-op business, 1946-1950 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 8)
      - 139 east 79th street: co-op business, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 9)
      - Green-Wood Cemetery: Noyes and Brown family plots, 1942-1950 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 10)
      - Montagu and Priscilla Norman; Sir Henry Clay, 1942-1952 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 11)
      - Emily deForest Webster; Frances deForest Stewart, 1943-1944, 1954 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 12)
      - Chester Jay Hunt: correspondence with George Parmly Day, Yale alumni agent, 1943-1945 (Offsite-box 103, Folder 13)
      - Chester Jay Hunt: correspondence with George Parmly Day, Yale alumni agent, 1946-1950 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 1)
      - Chester Jay Hunt, 1944-1954 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 2)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: Smith Park Realty Corporation stock, 1944-1950 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 3)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: correspondence with law firm Lord, Day, & Lord, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 4)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: finances and family correspondence, 1947-1954 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 5)
      - Anthony Clifton Brown, 1945-1953 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 6)
      - Workmen's Compensation: Arlene Tikkanen (Offsite-box 104, Folder 7)
      - Valuation of items stolen from Aurelia Clifton Brown's room, 1950 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 8)
      - Responses to book on 50 years with Brown Brothers, 1950 June - 1953 April (Offsite-box 104, Folder 9)
      - Moneyed capital tax on various family estates, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 10)
      - Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church Building Fund, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 11)
      - Winthrop Gilman Brown, 1952, 1954 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 12)
      - Eugene Delano Wadsworth, 1953 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 13)
      - Bound memorial minute: Bank for Savings in the City of New York, 1954 May 18 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 1)
      - Bound memorial minute: Gratuity Fund of the New York Stock Exchange, 1954 May 19 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 2)
      - Bound memorial minute: Atlantic Mutual Insurance Co., 1954 June 2 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 3)
      - Bound memorial minutes: Prudential Insurance Company of Great Britain / Hudson Insurnace Company of New York / Skandia Insurance Company of Stockholm, 1954 June 3 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 4)
      - Unbound memorial minutes: Commercial Union Assurance Co., The Phelps Association, Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church, 1954 June 4 - 21 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 5)
      - Bound memorial minute: Sun Insurance Office Ltd., 1954 September 23 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 6)
      - Obituaries and biographies; recipients of history of the firm, 1954, 1966 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 7)
      - Liverpool & London policy with James Brown as Chairman; supporting information, 1862, 1864, 1905-1907 (Offsite-box OS 9, Folder 10)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: Ardmore property, Durham & Irvine, 1934-1942 (Offsite-box OS 9, Folder 11)
      - James Crosby Brown estate: Hirst & MacFarland correspondence about subdivision plans, 1934 (Drawer OS 1900)
      - Green-Wood Cemetery: headstone and plans by John Crosby Brown Moore, 1939 (Drawer OS D1900)
      - Caro Noyes bride book, 1904-1905 (Offsite-box BBH-11, Volume 60)
      - Caro Noyes Brown diary, South American visit, 1929 January 29-April 7 (Offsite-box BBH-11, Volume 61)
      - Household inventory, 1932, 1943 (Offsite-box BBH-11, Volume 62)
    - Subseries C.ii. Business Records (1902-1952)
      The subseries includes correspondence and other records related to Thatcher Brown's service as a director of a variety of insurance and banking concerns, as well as his partnership at Brown Brothers & Co. and Brown Brothers Harriman.
      - The Bank for Savings in the City of New York: by-laws and reports, 1902, 1920, 1926, undated (Offsite-box 105, Folder 8)
      - The Bank for Savings in the City of New York: correspondence, 1920, 1921, 1925, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 9)
      - Brown Brothers: profit and loss statement; commercial credit analysis; travelers letters of credit, 1910-1932 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 10)
      - Brown Brothers New York operating expenses; comparison of ratios; general examination of results, 1913-1927 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 11)
      - Insurance company directorships, 1922-1943 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 1)
      - Insurance company directorships, 1928-1950 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 2)
      - Insurance company directorships, 1932-1954 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 3)
      - Insurance company directorships, 1938-1953 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 4)
      - James A Vaughan: loan, 1926-1947 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 5)
      - Carbon typescript of " 'Foreign' Securities", 1932 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 6)
      - Brown Brothers Harriman New York Stock Exchange seat, 1932, 1942 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 7)
      - West Virginia debt bonds; St. Louis Coke & Iron; Federal Coke and Chemical; SKF Industries; Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1933-1952 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 8)
      - Beaver Coal Company; West Virginia debt settlement, 1935-1940 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 9)
      - Davis Polk Wardwell Gardner & Reed; George A. Brownell correspondence about insurance and banking laws, 1938-1948 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 10)
      - Claus H. Vogel; Gillen; John Anderson; estate of Gherardi Davis; estate Thomas D. Thacher; Louis Curtis, 1939-1941 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 11)
      - Alfred Sarasin and William Gradenwitz, 1939-1950 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 12)
      - Directorships of Brown Brothers Harriman partners, 1949-1952 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 13)
    - Subseries C.iii. Financial Records (1891-1955)
      Scope and contents
      The subseries includes personal banking, tax, and estate financial materials from both Thatcher and Caro Noyes Brown, including the accounting for Mrs. Brown's estate and trusts under her will. The checks and desk checkbooks document payments to charitable organizations. The returned canceled checks and wallet checkbooks are boxed separately because of their size.
      - Account books, 1891-1897 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 14)
      - Bank book: The Bank for Savings, 1897-1941 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 15)
      - Income tax: calculations and forms, 1914-1918 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 1)
      - Income tax: 1918-1920, 1918-1929 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 2)
      - Income tax: 1921, 1922, 1921-1927 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 3)
      - Income tax: working papers, joint return Thatcher M. and Caro N. Brown, 1922 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 4)
      - Income tax: 1923-1926, 1923-1927 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 5)
      - Income tax: correspondence with Brown Brothers Harriman, 1928-1946 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 6)
      - Checkbook: charitable account, 1921-1926 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 7)
      - Checkbook: charitable account, 1926-1930 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 8)
      - Checkbook: charitable contributions, 1930 November 5 - 1934 November 28 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 1)
      - Caro Noyes Brown checks, checkbooks, bank books, 1934-1947 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 2)
      - Directors' fees from insurance companies, 1939-1948 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 3)
      - Checkbook: charitable account, 1941-1943 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 4)
      - Checkbook: charitable account, 1943-1948 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 5)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: will, trusteeship. securities, taxes, inheritance tax valuation, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 6)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: account settlements, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 7)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: appraisals, releases, jewelry distribution, final accounting, executors' final settlement, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 8)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: accounts with Brown Brothers Harriman, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 9)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: statements for trust under will, 1948-1951 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 2)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: trust statements and transactions, 1948-1954 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 3)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: trust income tax returns and statements, 1949-1953 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 4)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: income advices on ground floor, 139 east 79th street, 1949-1954 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 5)
      - Caro Noyes Brown estate: statements for trust under will, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 6)
      - Tax preparation: 1948 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 7)
      - Charitable contributions and deductible expenses, 1950-1954 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 8)
      - Tax paid for household employees, 1950-1955 (Offsite-box 109, Folder 9)
      - Checkbooks (1916-1917, 1920, 1936-1954), cancelled checks (1947-1954), 1916-1954 (Offsite-box 110)
      - Expense account, 1928-1933 (Offsite-box BBH-11, Volume 63)
  - Subseries D. Moreau Delano Papers (1931-1935), 1 volume, 1 folder